techattend.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy

Tech Attend cares how information about you is used and shared.  This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which we collect, use, maintain and disclose information collected from users of techattend.com.

You may be asked for an email address in case of subscribing to our newsletter. We will never share your email address to any third party. You may, however, visit our Site anonymously.

You may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, advertisers, sponsors, and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site.  Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non-personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

The [DoubleClick cookie](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/answer.py?answer=2839090) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit Tech Attend and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively,  you can opt out of some third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

We may collect non-personal identification information about you whenever you interact with our Site. This information is required only for optimal delivery of our content to the visitor’s computer.

Our Site uses “cookies” to enhance your browsing experience. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about you. You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

If you decide to opt-in to our newsletter, you will receive emails that may include news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

We promise to NEVER send you any spam. Please report to us if you receive any.

Tech Attend will NEVER ask for your Credit Card details, and we request that you do not enter it on our Site.

Tech Attend has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time.

For further information please [contact us](http://www.techattend.com/contact/)

Last Modified: November 05, 2013.
